

Suryam Sourya

Software developer

I currently pursing Bachelor of Engineering from computer Science final year. I am interested in developing web applications and I have expertise problem solving related to the natural problem around the world. I have also joined tech communities to enhance my skills. To work and deploy multiple project.

xuryamsourya8@gmail.com

BIHAR, INDIA

in linkedin.com/in/suryam-sourya

7288997526

1 01 February, 2002

github.com/suryam2048

EDUCATION

B.E Computer Science Engineering

Sathyabama university

08/2022 - Present Chennai /8.9 CGPA

HSC

Viswasanthi English medium

06/2017 - 05/2019 Vijaywada/85%

Courses

- PCM

SSC

Sri Prakash vidya Niketan

06/2016 - 05/2017 Visakhapatnam/9.6GPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer INFOCUS RESEARCH LAB

05/2023 - 07/2023 WFH

DBMS -INTERN

Database operation ,creating new Query, JQuery, search operation

Web Developer

Sathyabama university

09/2023 - Present

ALUMNI WEB APPLICATION

- connecting Alumni SIST

ACHIEVEMENT

SAP Hackthon (09/2021 - 09/2021)

web Application

Techno Summit (11/2022 - 12/2022)

software development

Web Contest SIST (02/2021 - 03/2021)

PROBLEM SOLVING APPLICATION

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JAVASCRIPT

ReactJS

nodeJS

ExpressJS

MongoDB

Business analystics

LINUX

PERSONAL PROJECTS

skipper web application (02/2023 - 03/2023)

- connecting multiple sports atlethes
- https://github.com/suryam2048/Skipperq/tree/master

Arts works and Gallery (09/2022 - 12/2022)

- E-commerce Web application for the selling painting and frames
- https://github.com/suryam2048/Artwork

CERTIFICATES

NVIDIA (02/2023 - 03/2023)

fundamental of deep learning

IBM (06/2023 - 07/2023)

HTML AND CSS WEB APPLICATION

TOOLS

VS-Code

Cloudinary

Mongodb

Studio 3D

Android Studio

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

HINDI

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

NETWORKING

Android Developement

Cyber Security